Guide to the National Guardian Photographs PHOTOS.213
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Oil & Gas Workers, 1952-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Restaurant/Hotel Workers, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Railroad Workers, 1951-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Sanitation, 1941-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Run-away Shops, 1986-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Demonstrations – Puerto Rico, 1976-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Puerto Ricans /U.S., 1964-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Puerto Rico – U.S. Demonstrations, 1964-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Puerto Rico, 1949-1986; 2.0 folders (Box 23, Folder 35-36)
- NYC – Power Blackout Nov. 1965, 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 37)
- NYC – Blackout 1977, 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 38)
- New York City Scenes, 1960-1966; 1.0 folder (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Nixon Cabinet, 1972-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Watergate – Impeach, 1972-1974; 2.0 folders (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
- Watergate, 1973-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Washington Admininstration (Watergate etal), 1973-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Assassinations, 1963-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Attica, 1971-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 7)
- American Bar Association, 1963-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Baltimore Two, 1976-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Berrigan/Kissinger, 1968-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Calley/Medina, 1969-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Capital Punishment – Legal System, 1960-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 12)
- CIA/FBI, 1963-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Chicago 8 Trial, 1968-1970; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 14)
- DACAJEWEIAH (John Hill), 1977-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Death Penalty, 1972-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Filipino Nurses, 1977-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Grand Jury Abuse, 1976-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Hollywood 10, 1947-1959; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 19)
- HUAC, 1951-1965; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Willie McGee Trial/Execution, 1951-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Rev. W. Melish, 1956-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Milwaukee 14, 1969-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Tom Mooney, 1931-1942; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 24)
- My Lai, 1969-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 25)
- NY 8+, 1982-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Oakland 7, 1969-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Oswald/Warren Report, 1959-1964; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Pendleton 14, 1977-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 29)
- James Earl Ray, 1968-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Jack Ruby Trial, 1962-1965; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Assata Shakur, 1972-1982; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Morton Sobell, 1954-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Sacco & Vanzetti, 1923-1959; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Scopes "Monkey Trial", 1957-1965; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 35)
- SLA, 1974-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Martin Sostre, 1960-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 37)
- S-Q 6 Trial, 1971-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Weather Underground, 1970-; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Trials – miscl., 1969-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Air Pollution, 1954-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Dams & Irrigation (conservation), 1940-1966; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Ecology, 1954-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Energy, U.S., 1970-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Military Weapons, 1957-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Nuclear, 1964-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Nuclear Energy & Weapons, 1971-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Panther Trials, 1969-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Police, 1965-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 49)
- Police Brutality, 1972-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 50)
- Police Demonstration, 1963-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 51)
- Prison & Prisoners – Legal System, 1947-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Soledad – San Quentin, 1970-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 53)
- Students for Democratic Society – Organizations & Groups, 1968-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 54)
- Supreme Court Portraits, 1953-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 24, Folder 55)
- International Organizations, 1975-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Australia, 1955-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Canada, 1963-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 3)
- New Zealand, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Europe, 1971-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 5)
- European Common Market, 1961-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 6)
- North Atlantic Treaty Organization – NATO, 1963-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Albania, 1962-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Austria, 1951-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Belgium, 1945-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Britain, 1959-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 11)
- England, 1967-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Bulgaria, 1947-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Czechoslovakia: 1968, Soviet Invasion, 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Czechoslovakia, 1947-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Finland, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 16)
- France – Demonstrations, protests, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 17)
- France – miscellaneous, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 18)
- France – Personalities, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 19)
- France: Racism, 1984-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 20)
- E. Germany, 1969-1982; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 21)
- West Germany, 1917-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 22)
- West German Left, 1983-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Greece, 1973-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Holland, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Ireland, 1973-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Italy – miscellaneous, 1950-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Portugal, 1974-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Romania, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Scotland, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Spain, 1972-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Sweden, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Turkey, 1959-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 33)
- U.S.S.R., 1943-1973; 2.0 folders (Box 25, Folder 34-35)
- Yugoslavia, 1979-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Korea’s War – China, 1948-1958; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 1)
- US & China, 1959-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Cultural Revolution China, 1966-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 3)
- War With Japan – China, 1940-1946; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Revolutions– China, 1945-1949; 2.0 folders (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
- Commerce – China, 1960-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 7)
- China – Agriculture, 1958-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Madam Sun-Yât Sen, 1944-1955; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Demonstrations & Congress China, 1951-1975; 2.0 folders (Box 26, Folder 10-11)
- China – U.N., National Day, 1970-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Peasants – China, 1951-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Industry – China, 1951-1975; 5.0 folders (Box 26, Folder 14-18)
- Political, Diplomatic Figures – China, 1943-1976; 2.0 folders (Box 26, Folder 19-20)
- Military – China, 1949-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Education – China, 1958-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Children – China, 1952-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Africa-General, 1973-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Algeria, 1963-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Angola, 1961-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Angola, 1958-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Angola – US Demonstrations, 1972-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Bechuanaland – Africa Botswana, 1965-; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Burundi, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Cameroon, 1956-1962; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Cape Verde Island, 1963-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Chad, 1972-; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Congo, 1961-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Dahomey, 1968-; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Eritrean Relief Committee, Inc., 1978-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Eritrea, 1977-1986; 2.0 folders (Box 27, Folder 15-16)
- Ethiopia, 1963-1990; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Gabon, 1974-; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Gambia, 1965-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Ghana, 1960-1966; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Guinea & Guinea-Bissau, 1960-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Eritrea & the Horn of Africa, 1965-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Ivory Coast, 1962-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Kenya, 1961-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Lesotho, 1966-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Liberia, 1961-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Libya, 1960-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Malawi, 1960-1962; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Mali, 1962-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Mauritania, 1974-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Morocco, 1954-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Sahara, 1975-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Mozambique, 1975-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Namibia, 1973-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Natal, 1972-; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Niger, 1973-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Nigeria, 1966-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Uman, 1972-; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Sao Tome & Principe, 1975-; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Senegal (Mali Federation), 1960-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 40)
- Somalia, 1966-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 41)
- South Africa, 1963-1989; 2.0 folders (Box 27, Folder 41-42)
- Sudan, 1970-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 43)
- Tanzania, 1964-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 44)
- Togo, 1958-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 45)
- Tunisia, 1955-1961; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 46)
- Uganda, 1962-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 47)
- Upper Volta, 1973-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Western Sahara, 1973-1988; 2.0 folders (Box 27, Folder 49-50)
- Zaire, 1960-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Zambia, 1965-1966; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Zanzibar, 1963-1964; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Zimbabwe (Rhodesia), 1959-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Latin America, 1962-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Organization of American States – OAS, 1960-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 6)
- OAS Punta Del Este Conference, 1962-; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Anguilla, 1969-; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Barbados, 1966-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Bermuda, 1960-1970; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Bolivia, 1963-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Brazil, 1958-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Chile, 1956-1987; 4.0 folders (Box 28, Folder 13-16)
- Colombia, 1960-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Costa Rica, 1955-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Curacao, 1969-; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Ecuador, 1955-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 20)
- El Salvador, 1962-1990; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 21)
- El Salvador (Earthquake), 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Refugees/El Salvador outside U.S., 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Grenada, 1980-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Guatemala, 1954-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Refugees/Guatemalan outside U.S., 1982-; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Guyana, 1953-1964; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Haiti, 1957-1987; 2.0 folders (Box 28, Folder 28-29)
- Honduras, 1969-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Jamaica, 1966-1981; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Panama, 1958-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Paraguay, 1957-1962; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Peru, 1956-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Trinidad, 1963-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Uruguay, 1971-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Venezuela, 1963-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Mexico, 1964-1989; 3.0 folders (Box 29, Folder 4-6)
- Mozambique, 1965-1989; 2.0 folders (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
- Philippines, 1970-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Philippines, 1956-1978; 2.0 folders (Box 29, Folder 10-11)
- Nicaragua, 1933-1990; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Nicaragua – Army, 1980-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Nicaragua – Contras, 1983-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Nicaragua – Education, 1983-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Nic Election, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Nicaragua – General Life in, 1979-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Nicaragua Solidarity, 1984-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Nicaragua: Health, 1981-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Nicaragua – Miskitos, 1985-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Obando y Bravo Archbishop of Nicaragua, 1984-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Daniel Ortega, 1984-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Nicaragua/ Religion, 1983-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Nicaragua – Personages, 1983-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Left Strategy, 1955-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Nica – Opposition, 1984-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Nicaragua – War Pix, 1983-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 1)
- South Africa (old), 1958-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Malaysia, 1959-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Micronesia, 1981-; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 4)
- New Caledonia, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Papua New Guinea, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Thailand, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Thailand, 1951-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Taiwan, 1958-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Laos, 1959-1986; 4.0 folders (Box 30, Folder 10-13)
- DPRK –North Korea, 1958-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Korea – 1940s-1950s, 1940-1959; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Personalities – South Korea, 1952-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Personalities – North Korea, 1965-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 17)
- South Korea, 1960-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 18)
- U.S. Demonstrations – Korea, 1973-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Korean War, 1947-1972; 2.0 folders (Box 30, Folder 20-21)
- Indonesia, 1948-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Japan, 1941-1983; 2.0 folders (Box 30, Folder 23-24)
- Kampuchea, 1982-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Korea – Negotiations/ Panmunjom, 1951-1957; 1.0 folder (Box 30, Folder 26)
- South Korea, 1949-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 1)
- DPRK – North Korea, 1953-1977; 2.0 folders (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
- Burma, 1954-1966; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Banding Peace Conference, 1955-1963; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Anna Louise Strong, 1955-1959; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 6)
- China & other Countries (visits etc.), 1949-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 7)
- China-Oversized Photos-Misc., 1972-; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 8)
- China: Party, Diplomats, etc., 1955-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 9)
- China – Mao, 1953-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Tibet, 1959-1960; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Mongolia – Outer, 1961-1965; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Agriculture – China, 1944-1976; 2.0 folders (Box 31, Folder 13-14)
- Forestry – China, 1956-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 15)
- China – Women, 1974-; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 16)
- China – Minorities, 1973-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 17)
- China – Army/Militia, 1972-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 18)
- China – Industry, 1959-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 19)
- China – Agriculture, 1974-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 20)
- China – Education, 1974-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 21)
- China – Art/Culture, 1974-; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 22)
- China – Leadership, 1971-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 23)
- China – Medicine, 1974-; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 24)
- China – Sports, 1974-; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 25)
- China Miscellaneous, 1967-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 26)
- China – Children, 1976-; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 27)
- China – Current, 1949-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Guam, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Hong Kong, 1949-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Israel After 1973 War, 1973-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Egypt After 1973, 1973-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Egypt – Between 1967 and 1973 Wars, 1969-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Egypt Before 1967, 1956-1964; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Saudi Arabia, 1949-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Afghanistan, 1963-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Cyprus, 1956-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 7)
- India, 1947-1987; 2.0 folders (Box 32, Folder 8-9)
- Pakistan, 1959-1972; 2.0 folders (Box 32, Folder 10-11)
- Nepal, 1960-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Sri Lanka, 1960-1982; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Iraq, 1958-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Rushdie – Iran Scandal, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Iran-Iraq War, 1983-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Iran, 1951-1982; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Jordan, 1956-1970; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Kuwait, 1961-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Lebanon, 1974-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Lebanon General, 1958-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Lebanon – Civil War, 1958-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Libya, 1972-; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 23)
- OPEC, 1973-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Palestinians, 1968-1973; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Palestine Current, 1969-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Palestinians – General Graphics and Pictures, 1967-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Syria, 1967-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Yemen/Aden, 1962-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 29)
- United Arab Emirates, 1976-; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Bangladesh, 1971-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Middle East, 1983-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Israel – miscellaneous see also Palestine, 1948-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 33, Folder 2)
- West Bank/Gaza, 1987-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Palestine – File, 1969-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Mideast – miscellaneous, 1969-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Israel thru 1948 War, 1946-1948; 2.0 folders (Box 33, Folder 6-7)
- Israel, 1948-1967; 1.0 folder (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Mideast war 1967, 1.0 folder (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Israel, 1976-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Israel between 1967 and 1973 Wars, 1968-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Mideast War – October 1973, 1973-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 33, Folder 12)